No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Hi, this is Tomoshiori.
This is how I am here at the ceremonial pitch today.
But that's not all my activities today, is it?
First of all, I am going to make a radio appearance before the game now.
Then, after that, I will appear on the Eagles Stage.
And then I will do the ceremonial pitch.
And I will also be the stadium MC.
And I will perform on the My Hero Towel Orlette.
In addition, I will also appear in 7 episodes of "Habatake Rakuteigurus," which is about 6 times in total.
I hope that I can make today's game more exciting in various ways than usual,
I will do my best to help in any way I can.
I have been cheerleading at the stadium for about seven years,
Today is the first time in about seven years. I will be dancing in the stadium, so please look forward to seeing how it goes.
I'm off. Yay!
Hello. Excuse me, Kubo from later.
I was running various videos on the day of the Fans' Match.
I was a little busy on the day, you know.
I didn't have much time to talk.
That's why I'd like to talk about it here.
Please understand that I'm going to do it in this way.
First of all, we recorded a radio program.
It's a program called "Angeles Room" that starts at 10:15 on Mondays.
Yes.
Haruka and I will talk about our junior days.
I'd like to talk about Haruka and the two of you when you were in junior high school.
We'd like five minutes of your time.
Yes, please.
When I was in junior high school, I was learning cheerleading.
Haruka, who was a teammate of mine when I was in junior high school.
She's a member of the Tohoku Golden Angels, who are currently dancing at the stadium.
She is a member of the Tohoku Golden Angels.
We were in the same class when we were in elementary school.
We were in the same class, and we participated in competitions together.
We participated in competitions together and danced together at the stadium.
So I was very happy.
I have a lot of experience.
Thank you very much.
Ho, ho!
Now I'm going to go to the Eagle Stage.
I've always seen many events on this stage, but this was the first time for me to perform on this stage.
I was nervous because it was the first time for me to perform on this stage.
After that, I went to the Lucky Eagles Academy.
Sujiggera Scalecher and Chimuchi
Ms. Shiori Kagoshima will appear on stage!
Let's smile together!
After this, Ms. Shiori Kubou will appear!
What do you think?
If you have a face, please hide it.
Yes, please hide low so that we can see the little one behind you.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll call her up now.
Today, we have an MC for the ceremony, the pitch, and the stadium.
Let's have Ms. Shiori Kubo, Borking Six, please!
It seems that the audience in front of the stage has been waiting for quite a while.
I was so grateful!
I was so happy to see so many people holding my towel that I collaborated with the Rakuten Eagles.
I was so happy!
Are there any players you are watching this season, or do you think their turn is good?
Well, young players have been remarkable, but
I've been rooting for Kurokawa since the year of his rise to prominence.
I would like to see him play more games this year.
Yes, that's true. I would like you to support us so that we can have more games.
Thank you very much.
Kurachi-kun is really cute!
But when I was a little girl, Kurachi was so popular that I couldn't ask him to take my picture.
I was too shy to ask for a picture.
That's why I was so happy to be able to talk to Kurachi at such a close distance.
We started practicing pitching for the annual pitch.
I saw a video of him playing catch.
I'm told that you can catch a ball after watching a video of me playing catch.
I can do it... originally!
Why is that?
My father was an experienced pitcher, so he let me hold a glove when I was a kid.
He gave me a glove when I was a kid.
I had a kid's glove for myself.
I used to play catch with my father.I used to play catch with my father.
Actually, I can play catch.
But I've never played catch at this distance.
So I was surprised that I could do it.
I was throwing well at that time.
This time, I tried the set position. Last time was in the windup position?
I thought it would be cool to throw from the set position as I watched the players compete, so I decided to try it this time.
I'm nervous.
Oops.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
I'm happy to bring this to you.
The best one I've ever had.
We've had quite a good one.
Best regards.
Congratulations.
I didn't touch my arm at all.
From this angle.
Eh, it's frustrating.
I just finished the ceremonial pitch.
Already.
What?
Okay, I'll go.
I'm so frustrated.
I wish I could show you a video of that practice. I really threw well in practice.
That's just an excuse. It's so frustrating.
But once again, I was so nervous about this one pitch that I didn't know what to do.
But when I thought that the players throw many, many pitches to make a game...
I realized that it's all about mentality, and I'm still lacking in technique.
I'm still lacking in technique, but my mentality is not up to par either.
But I have cheerleading later today, so I'll do my best to make up for it in the cheerleading competition.
I'm so frustrated, I can't think of anything else but frustration.
This is the second time for me to be the stadium MC, and I'm very nervous.
Okay, let's start with "Editing." Three, two, one.
The back of the second floor.
Marks, start!
Ready!
Yes, number 6, shortstop, number 34, Tsuyoshi Yamazaki.
OK, it's my first time. It's my first time. Thank you very much.
I was nervous, Stadium MC, but I was reading this from the back of the second floor.
So the Rakuten Iggles made a comeback in the back of the second floor. I was so happy.
Watch out for foul balls.
Here we go.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Foul balls, please.
Okay, thank you.
Chain point.
Next up, number 7, Wright.
Waiting for the MC to come on.
I was able to watch the game.
Watching the match from here as well.
There were quite a few operations that day, so
I couldn't watch the game at all.
Only time I could see the game was when I was the stadium MC.
I was able to see the game.
Nice batting, Sumitani!
Ready, go!
Nice batting by Sumiya!
I was so happy. I was so happy to be able to say "nice batting".
Left fielder Hiroto Higashi will bat first.
Ready, go!
Left fielder Hiroto.
Okay, thank you.
I'm going down.
It's fallen down.
He's flying!
We have five performances coming up.
We're going to do a cheerleading performance using these towels.
I've been doing towel performances since I was a Junion.
But isn't it great to be able to do it under your own name one day?
It's just that it's my first time to dance, and I've learned it at home.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm going to enjoy it and do my best!
This "My Hero Towel Oulette" shows the audience holding up the players' towels on the vision screen.
When the song ends, the audience is asked who will be the last one to be shown on the screen.
Actually, here are two people who came to check the cheerleading dance for a moment.
Haruka and Koharu, who I told you about earlier, said they used to be in the same class.
I thought it might be you too when I saw you.
I was so happy that Koharu was happy to see me again after a long time.
They used to be teammates, but this time they danced by my side all the time.Two of my former teammates danced by my side the whole time this time!
I'm so happy!
Was Koharu with you?
She was with me.
What a relief!
We will do our best in the Minnie Cup together!
Please do!
I was so nervous.
I made no mistakes.
If I got my song right.
When I used to dance.
I had this player's towel.
They give out the towels to the dancers in advance.
And depending on the time and the day.
I didn't know which player's towel they had.
I was always looking forward to it.
I wondered which player's towel
I always wondered which player's towel I would be holding
I was always excited.
It was so much fun.
It's been a long time.
I finished performing with towels 5 times.
It was so much fun to dance in the stadium after a long time.
It made me nostalgic!
Now I have to perform 7 times on the steep stairs.
This is also my first performance, so I will do my best!
High Kitchen
For a long time, if someone was practicing during the atmospheric
they would teach me the choreography.
When I used to learn, I would definitely hold the pom-poms with my
back, you have to hold the pom-poms behind your back.
I was supposed to have my feet in the shape of number 3, so you can see my habit of doing that.
I was out of this gate back then, too, so I missed it.
It was my first time to dance, so I was very nervous.
It's the most exciting time of the show.
I could hear the customers were very happy to see us.
I could see the smiling faces of the customers watching us dance.
I was very happy on that day, too.
Thank you very much.
Next time notice
We finished today's card after dancing 7 times under 9 steps.
It was a lot of fun.
While we were waiting for exactly 7 times, we were watching the election with everyone in Chua,
I was watching the election with Chua and thinking that it was time to dance,
I was thinking that I might be able to see the game again, since it is now the bottom of the 7th inning,
I would like to go see the game now so that I can see even a little bit more of it,
It was a really fulfilling day.
We danced, we threw, we played radio, and we were allowed on stage,
It was a lot of fun.
I would like to do it again sometime, a little bit, because the Ceremonial New Pitch was a disappointing result,
I hope we can do something again,
I would like to dance again, and I would like to do my best for the last 8th place.
It was fun to dance to the studio after a long time.
That was my day. Thank you very much.
Bye bye.